TAM, WEE JIE

Personal Particulars

Gender : Male
Race : Chinese
Age : 28 years old
D.O.B : 20/08/1988
Marital Status : Single

Nationality : Malaysian Citizen / Singapore PR

Mobile No. : 9867 1290

Email Address : elvisvjtam@gmail.com

Home Address: Ang Mo Kio



Career Objective

I have 2 years experience in-charge full set accounts in Singapore healthcare and venture capital fund industry. I am here seeking Senior Accounts Executive/ Payroll position (permanent/ contract), where I can use my experience contribute my analytical skill to the company that will give me an opportunity to develop my career.

Work Experiences

EC World Asset Management Pte Ltd

Industry : Investment

Company Profile : EC World Asset Management Pte. Ltd., the parent company of Singapore-based EC World Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT), which received support from both retail and institutional investors for its public offering, EC World REIT is the first Chinese specialised logistics and e-commerce logistics REIT to be listed on the SGX and will be focusing investments on a diversified portfolio of income-producing real estate primarily used for supply-chain management and logistics purposes.

Position Title : Senior Account Executive (3 months Contract)

- Account Receivable & Account Payable, Bank Reconciliation
- Prepare Variances Analysis for Month End Trial Balance

Reason to Leave: Non-renewable contract job

Fortune Capital Management Pte Ltd

Nov 2015 to Feb 2017

May 2017 to Jul 2017

Industry : Investment

Company Profile : Established in Singapore in 1999, the company enlarged scope of networking and business partners in Asia by including countries in the ASEAN region.

It focuses in high-tech investments, specifically in software, information technology, and the internet, areas which Singapore companies have strong domain knowledge and core competency. Fortune Singapore provides a valuable platform for investment companies to enter new markets in Greater China, USA, and ASEAN.

Position Title : Senior Account Executive

- Account Receivable & Account Payable, Bank Reconciliation
- Monitor company weekly Cashflow
- Prepare Profit and Loss Statement, Statement of Financial Position
- Report financial report to directors

- Quarterly GST submission to IRAS
- Prepare withholding tax form
- Assist in Annual Budgeting

Reason to Leave: Company closed

Singapore Medical Group Limited

Aug 2013 to Sep 2015

Industry : Healthcare

Company Profile : Incorporated in 2005, Singapore Medical Group (SMG) is a private specialist healthcare provider with a network of 22 specialties. SMG has a total of 11 clinics strategically located in Paragon Medical Centres with a growing network of associates clinics across Singapore and listed on the Singapore Stock Exchange (SGX) since 2009.

Position Title : Account Executive

- Account Receivable & Account Payable, Bank Reconciliation
- Others:
 - Prepare month-end closing inventory report & maintain fixed asset register
 - Update Audit Schedule & prepare quarterly GST report

Reason to Leave: Better exposure to gain experience from fund investment company.

Educational Background

London School of Business & Finance, ACCA (Level II)

Jan 2013 – Dec 2015

Advanced Diploma in Applied Accounting

London Chamber of Commerce and Industry, LCCI (Level III)

Jan 2011 – Dec 2011

Diploma in Computerized Accounting

Tunku Abdul Rahman College Kuala Lumpur

Jun 2006 - May 2008

Diploma in International Business

		Skills		
	Proficiency		Proficiency	
SAP	Intermediate	MS Office	Intermediate	
MYOB	Intermediate	MS Excel	Intermediate	
ACCPAC	Intermediate			
		Language Skills		
English, Chin	nese, Malay			
		Additional Info		

PERSONALITY:

Integrity, analytical, organized, positive work attitude, able to work independent, good leadership, able think out of box and pleasant personality.

LAST DRAWN : S\$3,200 EXPECTED SALARY : S\$3,300

AVAILABILITY : Aug 2017

(Kindly SMS or email me if there is no pick up the call. Thank you.)